In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to pronounce the OY as in TOY diphthong.
我们将学习如何发音 OY，如在 TOY 中的双元音。
Diphthongs are a combination of two sounds,
双元音是两个声音的组合，
so they have a starting position and an ending position.
所以它们有一个起始位置和一个结束位置。
This diphthong begins with the AW as in LAW vowel.
这个双元音以 LAW 中的 AW 元音开始。
As a part of the diphthong,
作为双元音的一部分，
the lips round more than they do for the pure vowel by itself,
嘴唇比单独发纯元音时更加圆，
like in the word LAW.
就像在单词 LAW 中一样。
OY.
OY。
The tongue is lightly lifted and shifted a bit back,
舌头轻轻抬起并稍微向后移动，
so the tip of the tongue is not touching anything.
所以舌尖没有接触到任何东西。
The ending position is the IH as in SIT vowel.
结束位置是 SIT 中的 IH 元音。
The lips relax,
嘴唇放松，
and the tongue comes forward.
舌头向前移动。
The tip lightly touches the back of the bottom front teeth,
舌尖轻轻触碰下前牙的后面，
and the top, front part of the tongue arches up towards the roof of the mouth.
舌头的前上部分拱向口腔的上部。
This brings the jaw back up.
这使下巴抬起。
Let's look at this sound up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这个声音。
The face inside the mouth is dark because the tongue has shifted back.
口腔内部是黑暗的，因为舌头向后移动。
For the second position,
对于第二个位置，
the corners of the lips have relaxed out,
嘴唇的两角放松，
and the front, top part of the tongue reaches up towards the roof of the mouth.
舌头的前上部分向口腔的上部伸展。
There's still some jaw drop.
下巴仍然有些下垂。
Here's the word TOY.
这是单词 TOY。
Again,
再来一次，
lips round for the first sound,
嘴唇在第一个声音时是圆的，
and relax for the second sound, as the tongue arches towards the roof of the mouth in the front.
在第二个声音时放松，舌头在前部拱向口腔的上部。
In a stressed syllable,
在重读音节中，
the OY diphthong curves up,
OY 双元音曲线上升，
then down.
然后下降。
TOY.
TOY。
OY.
OY。
In an unstressed syllable,
在非重读音节中，
it's lower and flatter in pitch,
音调更低更平，
as well as quieter and quicker.
同时也更安静更快。
OY.
OY。
The diphthong is unstressed in the word TABLOID.
在单词 TABLOID 中，双元音是不重读的。
OY.
OY。
Let's take a look at this word.
让我们看看这个单词。
The diphthong looks the same.
双元音看起来是一样的。
Lips rounded for the beginning position,
嘴唇在起始位置是圆的，
then relaxing out for the ending position,
然后在结束位置放松，
before the tongue tip flips up for the D.
在舌尖翻起发 D 之前。
But because the pitch is flatter and the syllable is quicker,
但由于音调更平，音节更快，
it sounds unstressed.
听起来是不重读的。
The OY diphthong.
OY 双元音。
Stressed.
重读。
TOY.
TOY。
OY.
OY。
Unstressed.
非重读。
TABLOID.
TABLOID。
OY.
OY。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Joyful.
Joyful。
OY.
OY。
Coin.
Coin。
Joyful.
Joyful。
OY.
OY。
Joyful.
Joyful。
Steroid.
Steroid。
OY.
OY。
Steroid.
Steroid。
Loyal.
Loyal。
OY.
OY。
Loyal.
Loyal。
Boy.
Boy。
OY.
OY。
Boy.
Boy。